https://www.hostingphotography.com/about/privacy-policy/

HostingWeb HostingSSD Web HostingVPS & Dedicated HostingWordPress ContinuityTestimonialsFAQAbout UsSupportClient AreaContact UsWeb Hosting GuideKnowledgebaseOrderWeb HostingSSD Web HostingTransfer Domain NamePrivacy PolicyYou are here:HomeAbout UsPrivacy PolicyLast Updated 15th January 2008Hosting Photography is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Hosting Photography Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Hosting Photography website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationHosting Photography collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Hosting Photography also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Hosting Photography. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Hosting Photography for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Hosting Photography Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Hosting Photography public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Hosting Photography does not read any of your private online communications.Hosting Photography encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Hosting Photography so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Hosting Photography is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Hosting Photography and Hosting Photography family of Web sites.Use of your Personal InformationHosting Photography collects and uses your personal information to operate the Hosting Photography Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Hosting Photography also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Hosting Photography and its affiliates. Hosting Photography may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Hosting Photography does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Hosting Photography may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Hosting Photography may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Hosting Photography, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Hosting Photography does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Hosting Photography keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Hosting Photography, in order to determine what Hosting Photography services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Hosting Photography to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Hosting Photography Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Hosting Photography or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Hosting Photography; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Hosting Photography, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Hosting Photography Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Hosting Photography’s pages, or register with Hosting Photography site or services, a cookie helps Hosting Photography to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Hosting Photography Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Hosting Photography features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Hosting Photography services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationHosting Photography secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Hosting Photography secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementHosting Photography will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Hosting Photography encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Hosting Photography is protecting your information.Contact InformationHosting Photography welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Hosting Photography has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Hosting Photography at support@hostingphotography.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.Share this pageFacebookTwitterGoogle+TestimonialsHosting Photography - Web Hosting for PhotographersI was referred to your company by a friend who had used your services to build her own company website. She could not say enough good things. I am so thankful that she referred me! Due to my small budget as a new small business owner, I had been using a very bland template website from a big name company here in the US, and was extremely unhappy with it from day 1. When I was quoted prices for a professional looking website, I was shocked and pleased and could not wait to get started! We are working on the website now and I cannot wait for my customers to see the finished product! Thank you, Ian, for your patience and professionalism!Mechelle Forgani,United Stateshttp://www.itsofftherack.com 7ads6x98y
